Seeing my husband off to work on the bed👋
make the bed
Making bed as soon as wake up
I heard making your bed every day increases your happiness✨
Holiday with good weather for the first time in a long time🎶
Drink a cup of cold water
Put away the dishes
Now my kitchen is clean✨
prepare breakfast
I eat fruits every morning!
Kyohou grape I received from my neighbor🍇
I'm looking forward to eating a few of these grapes these days😋🤍
I'll have a proper breakfast out later, so I'll go light
yogurt + blueberry + blueberry jam
(I decided to eat grapes later…)
Breakfast in the summer is usually a cold, light fruit or yogurt
I watch Chiikawa everyday🥰 It heals me…
Favorite music🤍
make to do list!
I’ll write down what I want to do today
On days when I am completely off, I write mainly about what I want to do (play and hobbies)✍️
It's going to be another good day✨
Brush my teeth when I’m  done eating breakfast
Washing face
Morning skin care items🧴
I often use only lotion and a high-moisture cream
I especially like this cream because it is so comfortable to use✨
I sometimes use this serum after lotion
makeup!
Base makeup on day’s off
On days when I'm home all the time,
I put a lightweight sunscreen base
The room gets a lot of sun, even on days I don't go out so I wear sunscreen every day
Concealer under the eyes
I've been using this face powder for about 5.6 years now.I love it so much that I don't know how many times I have repeated it!
It has good coverage, doesn't fall apart, and is light✨
Eyebrows are made with pencil and powder
Today’s eyeshadows🤍
I like to apply a combination of monochromatic eyeshadows🤍
I used two of my recent favorite monochromatic eyeshadows
Apply eyeliner and my eye makeup is done
(No mascara basically)
Finally, apply tint💄
It looked like this! Sorry for the lack of clarity💦
I love cosmetics, so makeup time is therapeutic🍃🤭
set my hair
Apply "Refalock Oil" to hair and let it set
I do my best to avoid damaging my hair on my days off, but I'm going out for a bit today, so I'll set it!
I really like this iron because it doesn't hurt my hair and the finish is moist✨
I want to do this better...
What to bring on a morning activity day📝
Handkerchief, mobile battery, earphone
Wallets, notebooks and schedulers, pencil cases, etc…
I'll bring a parasol
My favorite tops🤍
Perfumes often used on holidays
I'm thinking of changing the soil because my Benjamin Baroque didn't grow at all this year🥲
Such a good weather today!
It was the first sunny holiday in a long time☀️
Café time☕️
Campagne sandwich
Iced Starbucks Latte (short size)
Because of the nice weather, there seem to be more people than usual😳
I love Starbucks lattes🫶🏻
This was the first time I had this and the sweet and spicy sauce was delicious😋
After breakfast, I start working✍️
Scheduling for September✍️
Lately, I've had a lot of things I've wanted to do besides YouTube activities…
In order to operate the channel more efficiently for those…
I'm trying out different ways of using time, editing, etc…through trial and error
I put up a Momonga🐹
I've been cooped up all August so
I’m planning to go out a lot in September🚶‍♀️
Had a very good time!
I'm hoping it cools off soon so I can take my morning walk🍂🤭
I headed to supermarket
Once you decide on a menu and write it down, your shopping will be smoother✌️
I’m home！
Immediately put the food in the refrigerator
Do the laundry
I use detergent for room drying
IROKA
handsome leaf
↑This is the softener what I’m using! It smells too good to be happy💐
clean the room
I do vacuum almost every day🧹
I will ask my husband to wipe it down tomorrow🙎‍♂️✨
The room is not that big, so cleaning will be quick and easy✨
Charging!
Broom🧹
TV stand that easily collects dust
High part of dresser
Display shelf🐰
Desks are also wiped clean
My best display shelf✨
Recently, the Chiikawa collection has grown🐹🤍
I feel happy every time I look at it 🫶
My husband recently bought me this blanket
Just looking at it is cute and soothing🥹
Spray fabric mist and cleaning done!
make lunch!
pm 12:30
Make a 15-minute lunch
Salad is essential🥗
I eat tomato every day 🍅✨
Many vegetables🥗
Sprinkle with fried onions and cool it down
My favorite arrabbiata sauce🤍
Eggplant for pasta🍆
Cut into one bite
Dipping in a water for 5 mins
Put olive oil and fry ground beef
Fry until it’s cooked
Add a eggplant 🍆
Fry until the eggplants get softened
arrabbiata sauce🍅🌶
This sauce is very tasty and highly recommended✨(available at KALDI)
After frying for a while, add pasta
Make cheese sauce as well
Melting cheese, milk, salt and pepper
Cover with plastic wrap and microwave for 50 seconds to 1 minute
Melted cheese sauce is ready🧀
Plate it up and it’s done!
Easy to make authentic pasta!🤤✨
today's lunch
Arrabbiata looks like Bolognese🍅🌶
Cheese sauce on salads and pasta🧀
I'll have a cafe-style lunch 🍽
I didn't put cheese on it right away so it hardened😂
This too good! Eggplant and ground meat is the best combination!🤤✨
Carrot dressing I've been into lately🥕
I can eat salads more delicious✨
This is what I make and eat for lunch on my days off. It’s delicious and easy🍝
I forgot to do laundry😂
Laundry is done twice during the week and once on weekends
During this season, I always dry it indoors because insects come when I dry it on the balcony
The fabric softener smells really nice and soothing…✨
Housework done !
I paint my nails while watching the drama💅
I’ll use this today!
I basically use gel nails, but I also like polished nails because they are easy to take off✌️
I always apply the topcoat last because it makes the color last much longer🙆‍♀️
🎬Gossip girl
I really like this color, it's so pretty🤍(2 coats)
make milk tea
15:00
I’ll make my favorite royal milk tea
Turn off the heat just before the milk comes to a boil, and add 2 tea bags
Earl Grey Candice bought at KALDI
Very fragrant, syrup for tea🎶
Cover and let stand for 3-5 minutes and it’s  done!
Snacks are MUJIRUSHI pumpkin scones🎃
I want to eat the whole series someday🥹
home cafe
pumpkin scone,
royal milk tea
This is the happiest time🤤✨
I tend to hold back on snacks during the week, but I don't hold back on holidays to enjoy them to the fullest🤭
Prepare for the release of finished videos and organize data on weekdays!
Basically, I don't edit videos on weekends because I concentrate on shooting videos while taking a good rest
Instead, I'm cramming in video editing after work on weekdays💪
I can always doing my best because of your support!!!!
Thank you so much!🥰🤍
(asmr)
make dinner!
19:05
My husband has been working late lately, so dinner is late💦
I haven't made Possum in a long time!
250-400 g pork block, 2 garlic cloves, 2 ginger, green part of leek, 1/2 onion
Water 1000ml
2 tablespoons miso soup, 2 tablespoons sake
1 tablespoon soy sauce, 1/2 teaspoon salt, black pepper
Bring to a boil, remove lye and simmer over low heat for 50 minutes to 1 hour
Removing makeup at the same time!
Even if I don't take a bath yet, I'll try to get it off as soon as possible
I make my favorite egg kimbap
Mix 2 servings of rice (about 300g), sesame oil, ground sesame seeds, and salt
4 eggs🥚🥚🥚🥚
Beat the eggs with a little salt
I want the egg kimbap to be a uniform color, so we melt it well!
Add sesame oil and cook eggs
Bake each egg in 3 batches
The size of this egg pan is perfect for making egg kimbap✌️(It's a FIKA pan)
If it's not in the right shape but it's okay, because you can fix it at the end🙆‍♀️
I will shape it while it is still hot
The shape is now rounded✨
Make second one
▷▷▷
Spread rices on nori (seaweed)
Personally, this process is the hardest😂
Spread evenly and evenly, and press down tightly at the end
Put an egg on top and roll it up
First one's done✨
Kimbap makes me want to go to Korea🇰🇷✨
I'm sure I'll be able to go back there easily soon, and when I do, I'd love to do a Seoul food tour🤤✨
The second one wound up good too✌️
Finally, brush the top with sesame oil
Sprinkle with sesame seeds for extra flavor✨
Finished!
I also love kimchi cheese kimbap and bulgogi, which I sometimes make✨
The possum meat is ready!
Possum is surprisingly easy to make as all you have to do is add the ingredients and simmer🙆‍♀️✨
Korean lettuce🥬
*Sauce for possum
2 tablespoons gochujang (red pepper paste)
2 tablespoons miso
1 tbsp vinegar
2 teaspoons sugar
2 teaspoons sesame oil
1 teaspoon grated garlic
Finally, make wakame seaweed soup
Cut off the white part of the green onion
Put leeks and wakame seaweed in a pot
Seasoning: chicken soup stock, salt, sesame oil
The perfect soup for Korean cuisine✨
today's dinner
Korean food🤍
Tender possum simmered for one hour✨
Egg kimbap
Wakame seaweed soup✨
Lately, I've been watching Jojo Part 6, one episode every day✨
The possum is really good🥹✨
I think I might prefer possum to samgyeopsal🤭
Egg kimbap is also a great ministry!!
We both enjoyed it and had a full meal✨
Today my husband was working and I was off, so I was on housekeeping duty!
On the other hand, when my husband is off, he does it, so we split the housework about 50-50
I don’t like washing dishes but I still have a dishwasher✨
I recommend using a dishwasher because it saves water and gas and is said to pay for itself in a few years!
Finally, wash the sink
I clean around the stove with alcohol every day
I think it's time to wash them with a scrubbing brush... but I leave them after all😂
Finally, refill with alcohol and the job done✌️
skincare time
22:35
The skin care after bath still using sheet masks✌️
VT: cica vital mask
Apply a lot of serum and let it blend in
ma:nyo bifida biome complex ampoule
Finally, cover with cream and done!
ma:nyo face cream
Then, fruit time with my husband🍇✨
Brushing teeth later🪥
Use aromas for a good night's sleep
↑ I keep it next to my bed✨
(While I aim to get a good night's sleep, I can't stop using my phone before bed😂)
This is how I spend my days when I am active in the morning and mostly at home!
Thank you for watching 🎶